<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<EBOOK>
	<RECIPES>
		<RECIPE>
			<SHAREURL>http://starplus.startv.in/masterchef/tcrecipe.aspx?Page=1&amp;team=celebritychef&amp;sid=40</SHAREURL>
			<SUMMARY>Spanish Omelet recipe by Katrina Kaif</SUMMARY>
			<INGREDIENT>4 eggs\n
250 g potatoes (peeled and thinly sliced)\n
100 g mushroom\n
Olive oil for frying\n
Salt to taste</INGREDIENT>
			<PROCEDURE>Heat oil in a frying pan and fry the thinly sliced potatoes till they are a nice golden in colour.Remove them from the pan and keep aside. Place the pan back on the flame.Whisk eggs well but not till the mix is stiff.Saute the mushrooms and add them to the potatoes. Fold the mixture into the eggs. Pour the mixture into the frying pan. When the bottom is done flip the omelette. Serve with a typical Spanish style tomato sauce.
			Slit the chilli and remove the seeds. Toast the chilli on a hot plate for a minute\n
then add the raisins and keep aside. Add this to the hot stock, tomatoes, almonds and puree in a blender.\n
Heat oil in a pan and sautee the onions and garlic till translucent. Add the cinnamon.\n
Add the tomato puree mixture. Simmer to a boil and reduce the mixture to a sauce consistency Approximately 30 minutes.\n
Pass through a sieve before serving.Spatchcock is a term used in professional kitchens for \n
poultry that is split down the back and flattened, which reduces roasting or grilling time considerably.\n
In this recipe, the split chicken is first dry brined, then carrots and potatoes are layered on a double-burner griddle.\n
The bird is placed on an elevated rack above the vegetables for roasting.\n
Directions:\n
Using kitchen shears or a chef’s knife, cut the backbone out of the chicken; discard the backbone.\n
Place the chicken, breast side up, on a baking sheet and rub the chicken all over with the dry brine.\n
Cover with plastic wrap and refrigerate for 8 hours. Rinse the chicken thoroughly with cold water and pat dry with paper towels.\n
Set the chicken on a wire rack-lined baking sheet and refrigerate overnight.\n
Let the chicken stand at room temperature for 1 hour. Preheat an oven to 400°F.\n 
			</PROCEDURE>
		</RECIPE>
	</RECIPES>
</EBOOK>